<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TimeTable Demo</string>

    <string-array name="Main">
        <item>TimeTable</item>
        <item>Subject</item>
        <item>Faculty</item>
        <item>Resources</item>
        <item>Events</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Description">
        <item>A plan of the times when particular classes are to take place.</item>
        <item>All the required Subjects are available,Checkout as per your Requirement</item>
        <item>Body of educators,i.e. professors, or teachers,whose aim is to impart knowledge to the learners</item>
        <item>Good notes can provide a great resource for creating outlines and studying.</item>
        <item>All the App settings can be configured here</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Week">
        <item>Monday</item>
        <item>Tuesday</item>
        <item>Wednesday</item>
        <item>Thursday</item>
        <item>Friday</item>
        <item>Saturday</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Monday">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>PPL</item>
        <item>PPS</item>
        <item>Chemistry</item>
        <item>Essence of TK</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Tuesday">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>PPL</item>
        <item>PPS</item>
        <item>Chemistry</item>
        <item>Essence of TK</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Wednesday">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>PPL</item>
        <item>PPS</item>
        <item>Chemistry</item>
        <item>Essence of TK</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Thursday">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>PPL</item>
        <item>PPS</item>
        <item>Chemistry</item>
        <item>Essence of TK</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Friday">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>PPL</item>
        <item>PPS</item>
        <item>Chemistry</item>
        <item>Essence of TK</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Saturday">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>PPL</item>
        <item>PPS</item>
        <item>Chemistry</item>
        <item>Essence of TK</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Time1">
        <item>10:00AM-11:00AM</item>
        <item>11:00AM-12:00PM</item>
        <item>12:00PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>2:00PM-3:00PM</item>
        <item>3:00PM-4:00PM</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Time2">
        <item>10:00AM-11:00AM</item>
        <item>11:00AM-12:00PM</item>
        <item>12:00PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>2:00PM-3:00PM</item>
        <item>3:00PM-4:00PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Time3">
        <item>10:00AM-11:00AM</item>
        <item>11:00AM-12:00PM</item>
        <item>12:00PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>2:00PM-3:00PM</item>
        <item>3:00PM-4:00PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Time4">
        <item>10:00AM-11:00AM</item>
        <item>11:00AM-12:00PM</item>
        <item>12:00PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>2:00PM-3:00PM</item>
        <item>3:00PM-4:00PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Time5">
        <item>10:00AM-11:00AM</item>
        <item>11:00AM-12:00PM</item>
        <item>12:00PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>2:00PM-3:00PM</item>
        <item>3:00PM-4:00PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Time6">
        <item>10:00AM-11:00AM</item>
        <item>11:00AM-12:00PM</item>
        <item>12:00PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>2:00PM-3:00PM</item>
        <item>3:00PM-4:00PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Subjects">
        <item>Data Structures</item>
        <item>Mathematics III</item>
        <item>Discrete Mathematics</item>
        <item>Basic Electronics Eng</item>
        <item>Logic Switching Theory</item>
        <item>Environmental Science</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="DataStructures">
        <item>Unit1</item>
        <item>Unit2</item>
        <item>Unit3</item>
        <item>Unit4</item>
        <item>Unit5</item>
        <item>Books</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="MathematicsIII">
        <item>
           Functions of Complex Variables: Limits and continuity of function, differentiability and

analyticity, necessary  sufficient conditions for a function to be analytic, Cauchy-
Reimann equations in polar form, harmonic functions, complex integration, Cauchy’s

integral theorem, extension of Cauchy’s integral theorem for multiply connected regions,
Cauchy’s integral formula, Cauchy’s formula for derivatives and their applications.
        </item>
        <item>
            Residue Calculus: Power series, Taylor’s series, Laurent’s series, zeros and singularities,
residues, residue theorem, evaluation of real integrals using residue theorem, bilinear
transformation, and conformal mapping.
        </item>
        <item>
Fourier Series: Fourier series, Fourier series expansions of even and odd functions,
convergence of Fourier series, and Fourier half range series.
        </item>
        <item>
Partial Differential Equations: Formation of first and second order partial differential
equations, solution of first order equations, Lagrange’s equation, Nonlinear first order
equations, Charpit’s method, higher order linear equations with constant coefficients.
        </item>
        <item>
Fourier Series Applications to Partial Differential Equations: Classification of linear
second order partial differential equations, Separation of variables method (Fourier
method), Fourier series solution of one dimensional heat and wave equations, Laplace’s
    </item>
        <item>
R.K.Jain S.R.K Iyengar, Advanced Engineering Mathematics, Narosa
Publication, 4

th Edition, 2014.

2. B.S.Grewal, Higher Engineering Mathematics, Khanna Publications, 43rd
Edition, 2014.
. 3. Gupta Kapoor, Fundamentals of Mathematical Statistics, Sultan Chand
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="DiscreteMathematics">
        <item>
            Fundamentals of Logic: Basic Connectives and Truth Tables, Logical Equivalence,
Logical Implication, Use of Quantifiers, Definitions and the Proof of Theorems.
Set Theory: Set and Subsets, Set Operations, and the Laws of Set theory, Counting and
Venn Diagrams.
Properties of the Integers: The well – ordering principle, Recursive Definitions, Division
Algorithms, Fundamental theorem of Arithmetic.
        </item>
        <item>
Relations and Functions: Cartesian Product, Functions onto Functions, Special Functions,
Pigeonhole Principle, Composition and Inverse Functions, Computational Complexity.
Relations: Partial Orders, Equivalence Relations and Partitions.
Principle of Inclusion and Exclusion: Principles of Inclusion and
Exclusion, Generalization of Principle, Derangements, Rock Polynomials, Arrangements
with Forbidden Positions.
        </item>
        <item>
Generating Functions: Introductory Examples, Definition And Examples, Partitions Of
Integers, Exponential Generating Function, Summation Operator.
Recurrence Relations: First – order linear recurrence relation, second – order linear
homogenous recurrence relation with constant coefficients, Non homogenous recurrence
relation, divide and conquer algorithms.
        </item>
        <item>
Algebraic Structures: Algebraic System – General Properties, Semi Groups, Monoids,
Homomorphism, Groups, Residue Arithmetic, Group Codes and their Applications.
        </item>
        <item>
Graph Theory: Definitions and examples, subgraphs, complements and graph
Isomorpshim, Vertex degree, Planar graphs, Hamiltonian paths and Cycles, Graph
Coloring, Euler  Hamiltonian graphs, and Chromatic number.
Trees: Definitions, properties and Examples, Rooted Trees, Spanning Trees and Minimum
Spanning Trees.
        </item>
        <item>
Tremblay J P, and Manohar R, Discrete Mathematical Structures with Applications
to Computer Science, Tata McGraw Hill Education, 2001.
2. Shanker Rao G, Mathematical Foundations of Computer Science,
I K International Publishing House Pvt. Ltd., 2006.
3. Mott Joe L Mott, Abraham Kandel, and Theodore P Baker,
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="BasicElectronicsEng">
        <item>
            Semi Conductor Theory: Energy Levels, Intrinsic and Extrinsic Semiconductors,
Mobility, Diffusion and Drift current. Hall Effect, Characteristics of P-N Junction diode,
Parameters and Applications.
Rectifiers: Half wave and Full wave Rectifiers (Bridge, center tapped) with and without
filters, ripple regulation and efficiency. Zener diode regulator.
        </item>
        <item>
Bipolar Junction Transistor: BJT, Current components, CE, CB, CC configurations,
characteristics, Transistor as amplifier. Analysis of CE,CB,CC Amplifiers(qualitative
treatment only).
        </item>
        <item>
Feedback Concepts – Properties of Negative Feedback Amplifiers, Classification,
Parameters .
Oscillators – Barkhausen Criterion, LC Type and RC Type Oscillators and Crystal
Oscillators. (Qualitative treatment only)
        </item>
        <item>
Operational Amplifiers – Introduction to OP Amp, characteristics and applications –
Inverting and Non-inverting Amplifiers, Summer, Integrator, Differentiator,
Instrumentation Amplifier.
Digital Systems: Basic Logic Gates, half, Full Adder and Subtractors.
        </item>
        <item>
Data Acquisition systems: Study of transducer (LVDT, Strain gauge, Temperature,
Force).
Photo Electric Devices and Industrial Devices: Photo diode, Photo Transistor, LED,
LCD, SCR, UJT Construction and Characteristics only.
Display Systems: Constructional details of C.R.O and Applications.
        </item>
        <item>
Jocob Millman, Christos C. Halkias and Satyabrata Jit, Electronics Devices and
Circuits”, 3rd Edition, McGraw Hill Education (India) Private Limited, 2010.
2. Rama Kanth A. Gaykward, Op-AMPS and Linear Integrated Circuits, 4
th Edition

Prentice Hall of India, 2000.
3. M. Morris Mano, Digital Design, 3rdEdition, Prentice Hall of India, 2002.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="LogicSwitchingTheory">
        <item>
            Boolean Algebra: Axiomatic definition of Boolean Algebra Operators, Postulates and
Theorems, Boolean Functions, Canonical Forms and Standard Forms, Simplification of
Boolean Functions Using Theorems and Karnaugh Map Method.
        </item>
        <item>
Minimization of Switching Functions: Quine-McCluskey Tabular Method,
Determination of Prime Implicants and Essential Prime Implicants.
Combinational Logic Design: Single-Output and Multiple-Output Combinational Circuit
Design, AND-OR, OR-AND and NAND/NOR Realizations, Exclusive-OR and
Equivalence functions.
        </item>
        <item>
Design of Combinational Logic Circuits: Gate Level design of Small Scale Integration
(SSI) circuits, Modular Combinational Logic Elements- Decoders, Encoders, Priority
encoders, Multiplexers and De-multiplexers.
Design of Integer Arithmetic Circuits using Combinational Logic: Integer Adders –
Binary Adders, Subtractors, Ripple Carry Adder and Carry Look Ahead Adder, and Carry
Save Adders.
        </item>
        <item>
Design of Combinational Circuits using Programmable Logic Devices (PLDs):
Programmable Read Only Memories (PROMs), Programmable Logic Arrays (PLAs),
Programmable Array Logic (PAL) devices.
Introduction to Sequential Circuit Elements: Latch, Various types of Flip-Flops and
their Excitation Tables.
        </item>
        <item>
Models of Sequential Circuits: Moore Machine and Mealy Machine, Analysis of
Sequential Circuits-State Table and State Transition Diagrams. Design of Sequential
Circuits-Counters. Moore and Mealy State Graphs for Sequence Detection, Methods for
Reduction of State Tables and State Assignments.
        </item>
        <item>
M Morris Mano and Michael D Ciletti, Digital Design, Prentice Hall of India,
Fourth Edition, 2008.
2. Zvi Kohavi, Switching and Finite Automata Theory, Tata McGraw Hill,
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="EnvironmentalSciences">
        <item>
            Environmental Studies: Definition, scope and importance, need for public awareness.
Natural resources: Water resources; use and over-utilization of surface and ground water,
floods, drought, conflicts over water, dams:benefits and problems. Effects of modern
agriculture, fertilizer- pesticide problems, water logging and salinity.
        </item>
        <item>
Ecosystems: Concept of an ecosystem, structure and function of an ecosystem, producers,
consumers and decomposers, energy flow in ecosystem, food chains, ecological pyramids,
aquatic ecosystem (ponds, streams, lakes, rivers, oceans, estuaries).
Energy resources: Growing energy needs, renewable and non-renewable energy sources.
Land Resources, land as a resource, land degradation, soil erosion and desertification.
        </item>
        <item>
Biodiversity: Genetic species and ecosystem diversity, bio-geographical classification of
India. Value of biodiversity, threats to biodiversity, endangered and endemic species of
India, conservation of biodiversity.
        </item>
        <item>
Environmental Pollution: Causes, effects and control measures of air pollution, water
pollution, soil pollution, noise pollution, thermal pollution; solid and liquid waste
management.
Environment Protection Act: Air, water, forest and wild life Acts, enforcement of
environmental legislation.
        </item>
        <item>
Social Issues and the Environment: Water conservation, watershed management, and
environmental ethics. Climate change, global warming, acid rain, ozone layer depletion.
Environmental Disaster Management: Types of disasters, impact of disasters on
environment, infrastructure, and development. Basic principles of disaster mitigation,
disaster management, and methodology. Disaster management cycle, and disaster
management in India.
        </item>
        <item>
A.K. De, Environmental Chemistry, Wiley Eastern Ltd.
2. E.P. Odum, Fundamentals of Ecology, W.B. Sunders Co., USA.
3. M.N. Rao and A.K. Datta , Waste Water Treatment, Oxford and IBK Publications.
4. Benny Joseph, Environmental Studies, Tata McGraw Hill, 2005.
5. V.K. Sharma, Disaster Management, National Centre for Disaster Management,
        </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Unit1</item>
        <item>Unit2</item>
        <item>Unit3</item>
        <item>Unit4</item>
        <item>Unit5</item>
        <item>Books</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="faculty_name">
        <item>Dr Shabbeer</item>
        <item>Mohiuddin</item>
        <item>Maniza Hijab</item>
        <item>Krishna Keerthi</item>
        <item>Manjusha</item>
        <item>Amanullah</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="DrShabbeer">
        <item>965324187</item>
        <item>shabbeeer45@gmail.com</item>
        <item>CSE Block 5th Floor R.No:5506</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Mohiuddin">
        <item>965324186</item>
        <item>mohiuddin45@gmail.com</item>
        <item>CSE Block 4th Floor R.No:5505</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ManizaHijab">
        <item>965324185</item>
        <item>maniza45@gmail.com</item>
        <item>CSE Block 3th Floor R.No:5506</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="KrishnaKeerthi">
        <item>965324184</item>
        <item>krishna45@gmail.com</item>
        <item>CSE Block 2th Floor R.No:5506</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Manjusha">
        <item>965324183</item>
        <item>manjusha45@gmail.com</item>
        <item>CSE Block 1st Floor R.No:5506</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Amanullah">
        <item>965324182</item>
        <item>amanullah45@gmail.com</item>
        <item>CSE Block 0th Floor R.No:5506</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
